mundu.tv 2013-03-20

# Terms - Mundu TV

|   
---  
   
|  |  |    
---  
Privacy PolicyMundu TV  
  
Your privacy is very important to us. We at Geodesic Limited ("GEODESIC") are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. GEODESIC does not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for any of their purposes, whether it is marketing or otherwise.

“Personal Information” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a name, a date of birth, an email address or other related information.

GEODESIC strives to protect your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained, although legal requirements may vary from country to country, and there may be countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information.

All the subsidiaries and affiliates of GEODESIC operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy"). However, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that GEODESIC does not own or control, or to people that GEODESIC does not employ or manage. 

Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which GEODESIC uses and protects your Personal Information.   
   
1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION  
1.1 GENERAL   
  
We collects information that is either anonymous or personally identifiable. Anonymous information refers to data that cannot be tied back to a specific individual, such as sources from where you update yourself about the latest software and applications for your device, or Internet sites you use to download and buy new software. 

Personally identifiable information refers to data with respect to who you are, such as your Name, Date of Birth, Gender, Country, Email Id as etc.   
1.2 CHILDREN   
  
We recognizes that children, including young teens, may not be able to make informed choices about personal information requested online. Accordingly, We does not target children or teenagers (younger than eighteen years of age) for collection of information online. We does not solicit or collect customer identifiable information targeted at children and teenagers under eighteen. We will encourage children to seek the consent of their parents before providing any information about themselves or their households to anyone on the Internet. We encourages parents to take an active role to protect the privacy and security of their children and to prevent the inappropriate use of information about their children.  
  
2\. USE OF INFORMATION   
2.1 USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION BY GEODESIC  
  
In general, you can visit this website/wapsite without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. However, most areas of this website/wapsite require registration to access. We collect this information to better understand your needs and provide you with services that are valuable to you. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit much of this website/wapsite.

As a condition to being allowed to download software from this website/wapsite, you may be asked for your Personal Information to enable GEODESIC and/or one of their affiliates, representatives or partners, to contact you from time to time by either email, postal mail, telephone and/or facsimile; to provide you with the information about any software downloaded from our website/wapsite and/or other products and/or services offered by GEODESIC or its affiliates or partners that we or they think may be of interest to you; to resolve disputes; to troubleshoot problems; to measure consumer interest in our products and services; to customize your experience; or to detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity.

You agree that we may use Personal Information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the website/wapsite's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the website/wapsite and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the website/wapsite.  
  
2.2 DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
  
As a matter of policy, GEODESIC does not sell or rent any of your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing, research or any other purposes. However in certain circumstances, it is possible that Personal Information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to laws, judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.  
  
3\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY  
  
GEODESIC will limit access to your Personal Information to its employees who reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to perform their responsibilities as employees. GEODESIC has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with relevant regulations to protect Personal Information about you.   
  
4\. ACCESS AND ACCURACY  
  
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, GEODESIC wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where GEODESIC collects Personal Information from you on the Web, its goal is to provide a means of contacting GEODESIC should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to support@mundu.tv and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.  
  
5\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY   
  
GEODESIC may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Personal Information or by placing a prominent notice on our website/wapsite.  
  
6\. QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS   
  
If you are a consumer with concerns about the our online privacy policy or its implementation you may contact us at +91-22-28311849 or email us at support@mundu.tv  
  
7\. YOUR CONSENT  
  
By using this website/wapsite and providing your Personal Information, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to GEODESIC's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where GEODESIC collects Personal Information on the website/wapsite.
